floridastateparks.org 2017-04-11

# Privacy Policy | Florida State Parks

Some content on this website is saved in an alternative format. To view these files, download the following free software or you can skip to the main content if you already have the appropriate readers. 

  * Use Adobe Acrobat to read Portable Document Format (PDF) files: [Download Adobe® Reader®](http://get.adobe.com/reader/ "External Link for Adobe Reader")
  * Microsoft Word file viewer and converter programs to enable those who do not have MS- Word or have another version of MS-Word to open and view MS-Word files: [Download Word file Viewer](http://www.microsoft.com/downloads/details.aspx?familyid=3657CE88-7CFA-457A-9AEC-F4F827F20CAC&displaylang=en "Link to MS Word Viewer download")
  * Microsoft offers Microsoft Excel file viewer and converter programs to enable those who do not have MS-Excel or have another version of MS-Excel to view MS-Excel files:[Download Excel file viewer](http://www.microsoft.com/downloads/details.aspx?FamilyID=1cd6acf9-ce06-4e1c-8dcf-f33f669dbc3a&DisplayLang=en "link to MS Excel download")

Under Florida law, email addresses are public records. If you do not want your email address released in response to a public records request, do not send electronic mail to this entity. Instead, contact this office by phone or in writing.

###  **Internet Privacy Policy**

Thank you for visiting the Florida State Parks online Park Guide, [FloridaStateParks.org](http://www.floridastateparks.org/). Your privacy is important to us. Simply stated, our policy is to collect no personal information about you when you visit us online, unless you affirmatively choose to make such information available to us.

When you visit this website, the web server automatically recognizes only the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed the site. This information does not result in the identification of your personal email address or other personal information.

In addition, information is only gathered regarding the volume and timing of access to the site by collecting information on the date, time and pages you visited while at the site. This is done so that the content of the site can be improved and your personal information is not identified.

If you choose to share personal information, such as by subscribing to a newsletter, sending a message or filling out an electronic form with personal information, the information will be saved for a designated period of time to comply with the state of Florida's archiving policies. However, information will not be disclosed to third parties or other government agencies, unless required by state or federal law. Please note that Florida's public records law requires that all information received in connection with state business be made available to anyone upon request, unless the information is subject to a specific statutory exemption.
